I won't let you die on me, Rohan,
hang in there!
So it picked up on my scent, huh?
So it's gonna hunt me down,
and feed on my body's nutrients
the moment it gets
its creepy feet on me, huh?
I got it!
It can't travel faster than 60km/h!
This bike'll be able to
outpace him easy.
But finding the user…
how the hell am I going to do that?
Okay, first things first,
I gotta think about this logically.
To start, why'd he lay his trap
in the inside of a tunnel
of all places?
You'd think ambushing us
from the side of the road
would be easier.
Second, there must be more to
his nutrient feeding
than meets the eye.
There must be some significance
to the tunnel.
I've gotta investigate!
I've gotta dig up every piece
of info on that Futatsumori Tunnel!
Koichi!
I'll call Koichi and have him
use Reverb to find the user!
Hey, hey.
What's got you all riled up?
It's okay…
There.
No way he's anywhere near me now.
Where's that card?
How the hell…?!
How'd he just appear
out of thin air?
I was driving at 80km/h,
his top speed is only 60km/h.
A simple calculation tells you
he should've arrived
two minutes after me.
That thing is a Stand.
It can disappear and reappear
wherever it wants…
It figures out your rough location,
then appears and…
homes in for the kill by scent!
S-Sixty kilometers…
W-What?!
- Shit! A baby carriage!
- What's wrong?
You're in such a foul mood…
If I slow down, I'm a dead man.
Rohan won't make it either.
Sorry, but hanging around
is a no go.
I've gotta just gun it!
All right Shining Diamond!
Do your thing.
Good!
At this rate,
I'll never be able to call Koichi!
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
EPISODE 29
HIGHWAY GO GO, PART 2
All right, Yoshioka.
In exactly one minute,
you will receive
an extremely important call.
This deal's worth one billion yen!
Failure is not an option!
Don't disappoint me, Yoshioka!
I gotcha, Boss!
Just leave it to me.
This'll work! Of course…
a cell phone!
It showed up at the nick of time.
Lucky!
I promise, sir,
I'll do everything in my power!
- Guess I do have a guardian angel!
- Um, hello?
Huh?
Dammit! One billion yen!
Shit, did I break it
when I grabbed it?
Where the hell is
my guardian angel now!
If you hate me, then just hang up!
H-How could you say that, Mina yo?
Spit it out! Ask her to be your wife!
Mina yo, will you m-marry—
So it is my lucky day.
- Now that's what I call good timing!
- Huh? What? What is it, Akira?
Hello, Hirose residence.
Koichi!
So that's the deal.
If I don't find the user,
I'm toast.
The guy must be obsessed
with the tunnel.
Like he has some kind of
grudge or something.
Any incidents
involving that tunnel?
Th-There is. It was published
in the paper two days ago.
I saw it on the news, too.
Some biker guy was drunk driving,
and crashed into
the tunnel's entrance.
Supposedly he's unconscious
and covered in bruises.
He's in intensive care
at Budogaoka Hospital now.
Sounds like the Stand got him, too.
Anything else?
Give me a sec.
I remember there was blood
all over the road.
The Stand feeds on
people's nutrients, right?
His victims would look different.
Maybe this guy from
the motorcycle accident
actually became the Stand user.
So he leeches nutrients
from others to heal himself..
What? I-It's the ocean!
I'm headed straight for
the cold, dark deep!
I gotta turn somewhere,
or I'm gonna dive head first
into that water!
That corner!
- I have to keep it over 60km/h!
- Hello? Josuke? What's wrong?
Koichi! Stay with me.
Don't hang up!
This is it… shit!
Crap! I think I'm gonna crash!
No.
If anyone can do it,
it's Josuke Higashikata.
I can do this. I will do this!
Yes! I made the turn!
Didja see that?!
Screw you, asshole!
W-What?!
More ocean!
NO ENTRY
The Port of Morioh!
Shining Diamond!
See that broken wall…
Fix it!
Th-That was close…
It was charging straight at me,
and was totally blind to the wall.
Like a mosquito
that can't see a screen,
it was pursuing me by scent alone.
Its attacks aren't thought out
or premeditated.
Its only objective is
to drain me of my nutrients.
That theory about this guy
being from the accident
is starting to make sense.
The pieces are coming together.
Josuke!
Koichi, the guy at the hospital!
That guy from the accident
has to be the Stand user!
Find his name.
Got it.
Damn, this situation sucks…
H-How am I gonna get out of this?
Where did Josuke go?
That meddlesome little shit…
I admit, when you took aim at
that nearly dead punk biker
as your next pin cushion,
You're crazy, crazy,
I thought, but…
You're astonishing! Incredible!
Who'd have thought that kid
would bring forth Highway Go Go?
Stands really are a manifestation
of the soul…
The hungrier their spirit,
the more intense their power!
The insatiable hunger
to heal oneself is unstoppable.
But oh how nice it would've been
to witness Josuke bite the dust!
What do I do? What do I do?
A ditch!
Finding a ditch that empties
into the ocean helps,
but he keeps closing in on me.
H-How do I make my getaway?
So, which one?
Let's see… The ocean's behind me,
which means it's also to my right.
I've gotta steer clear
of the water.
I came from the left… I think.
W-Which way do I go now?
I feel like the ocean's
to the left,
but if it's to the right…
Th-There's the middle, too…
W-What's happening?
I'm gunning it,
but I'm slowing down…
I-Is it busted?
W-What?! It's working just fine.
Then why can't I accelerate?
I'm grinding to a halt!
I-It's coming!
Could it be…
Am I out of gas?
Man, you had me
freaking out there for a second.
I'm just out of gas…
That's no sweat at all.
I was worried I had
a major wreck on my hands
that even Shining Diamond
couldn't fix.
Nope, I'm not stressing.
I can get out of this, easy peasy.
Still no problem.
Little tweak here…
A little modification there…
Though that thing teleports,
so I guess I can't get
too comfortable…
The gasoline, however,
is taken care of.
But…
I guess there is
one little problem…
Where the hell am I…
How the hell do I get to
that freak in hospital?
HIGHWAY GO GO
BUDOGAOKA
GENERAL HOSPITAL
Excuse me. I'm in a real pinch.
I have to know how I can find
the young man from
the Futatsumori Tunnel accident.
What's his room number?
You have to tell me!
Listen little man…
I suggest you read
that sign over there.
VISITING HOURS HAVE CONCLUDED
FOR TODAY.
Huh?
If you need your eyes examined,
come back tomorrow morning at 9:30.
Um, I'm not here for a visit.
There's a reason
I need to know his name!
This is serious.
You have to tell me!
Perhaps you didn't understand.
I said go home.
You know, it's pesky kids like you
who really make life difficult
for us adults.
You're pretty shrimpy for someone
belonging to a biker gang.
Do your feet even reach the ground?
Give me a break.
Act 3…
Okay, Master! Let's kill da ho!
Beeetch!
O-Oh, no!
That was close…
These are 50,000 yen a bottle.
Huh?
They're so heavy?!
They're going to fall!
Hey, you! Help me! Hold me up!
That "Hey, you!"
wasn't meant for me, was it?
Yes! You're the only one in here.
I don't know how much longer
I can hold this…
Well, that's all fine and good…
You did just tell me to go home.
I mean, I am shrimpy,
so I probably couldn't reach.
Is your superior going to
reprimand you if those break?
That would be sort of
an oh my god moment, wouldn't it?
All right, fine! I'll tell you!
He's in room 525!
Yuya Fungami is in 525.
Take that elevator
to the fifth floor!
Huh?
Josuke!
Koichi…
Figure it out, Koichi?
Room 525! His name is Yuya Fungami!
It's room 525!
Thanks, Koichi!
It's on the fifth floor!
Just take the elevator!
Sh-Shit…
He's slipping his way in!
Koichi! Reverb Act 3!
You're a man I can always count on.
Thanks, Koichi!
But 3 Freeze can focus its attack
on only one place at a time.
The rest of them
are going after Josuke!
There it is! Room 525!
I can't believe I made it!
The vent!
You bastard!
Only a few meters left to the room…
Why'd it have to be so far away!
I'm gonna kick your ass,
if it kills me!
So that's the bastard!
I'm gonna get to that bed… I swear!
I'm gonna get to that bed
and kick your ass…
Who the hell is this punk?
You're in Yu's room!
This isn't your room, idiot!
Leave that loser alone.
You don't look so hot…
I thought it had been a while
since that first guy in the tunnel
gave me his nutrients…
So you're the second sap
I've been chasing around, huh?
It's commendable
you made it this far.
I'm kinda shocked, actually.
Yu, you know this guy?
Huh?
Nope, never seen him in my life,
don't really care either.
Nice goin', Highway Go Go.
I'm feeling a lot better already
Now if I can just get a hold of two
or three more guys like this one,
I'll be able to make
a full recovery
Hey!
We told you, get your ass up
and get the hell out!
And I told you to leave
that loser alone!
Now get over here and
give me some love and attention.
Remember, poor Yu over here
is still stuck in bed.
I really have to pee. I don't know
how much longer I can hold it.
Ooh! Time for me to get to work!
We all agreed we'd be taking turns!
I'm up now!
What? No, it's me!
It doesn't matter who does it.
Just bring that piss bottle
and help me out.
Okay!
Then I'll…
Hey, Akemi.
That peach is rotten.
Fix me another one.
How do you know it's rotten?
How? Take a whiff.
Any idiot can tell it's rotten.
From over there?
You know, you have a point.
My sense of smell
must have gotten better.
Oh, you're right…
It really is rotten.
One of you three
is on your period, right?
Am I wrong? Someone's
on her period, right?
Huh?
Ha, so it's you, Yoshie!
Hit the nail on the head.
And one of you
is also really pissed, right?
When agitated,
the body secretes adrenaline,
and it's glaringly obvious
to my nose.
What got under your skin…
Is it you, Reiko?
Huh? I'm not angry or anything.
We couldn't be happier
you're feeling better baby.
Yeah, we're happy as a clam!
Yeah, nobody here's mad at all.
Hey, hey, something's wrong.
Somebody's downright furious,
and I can smell it loud and clear.
You better not be fibbing.
Which one of you
is seething on the inside?
You're looking at him.
That full-bodied eau de adrenaline…
Is courtesy of yours truly!
That's bullshit!
Your body should be
a nutritional waste land by now!
How are you standing?
Because…
You were sipping on my IV?
It was just a sampling,
but it was enough
to perk me up a bit.
I want you to release Rohan, now.
He's the guy you're
holding captive in the tunnel!
Imbecile!
Highway Go Go
hasn't forgotten your scent!
Yu, baby!
You three, keep your mouths shut!
My name is Josuke Higashikata.
Stand name, Shining Diamond.
I might be limited to
close-range attacks,
but I can assure you
my punching speed
is a lot faster than
a nap-inducing 60km/h.
I've never measured,
but close up,
I can get up to about 300km/h.
Hey, wait right there!
M-My back's broken.
I have fractured arms and legs,
I can't even roll over.
I'm majorly hurt!
You're gonna slap around a feeble,
bed-ridden hospital patient?
All right, I was a jerk.
I'll free the guy in the tunnel.
I think he's still alive.
Though it wouldn't hurt
to give him some nutrients…
S-So…
You wouldn't beat up
a poor invalid…
You wouldn't do something
so cowardly, would you?
That certainly
wouldn't be very manly!
Yeah! You coward!
Yeah, suppose you're right…
Knocking the shit out of
a poor injured victim
would leave a bad taste
in my mouth.
It's definitely not manly…
It's just not right.
Right? Beating up a guy like me
will haunt your conscience forever.
Which is why I already
made you all better.
Huh?!
Eh?
See if you can move.
You can, right?
You're completely healed,
aren't you?
You're right, I am…
Right.
By fixing you up real good,
I avoid looking like
a coward, right?
Yuya Fungami's hospital stay—
extended
If you so much as think about
healing yourself with
Highway Go Go,
I'll just rearrange your face
all over again, insisted Josuke.
I feel invigorated.
I feel like I've put on
a fresh pair of undies
in the wee hours of New Year's day.
- Yu, babe!
However, being nursedback
to health by a do ring fan girls
isn't too shabby either.
Meanwhile, Rohan…
Josuke Higashikata…
U-Um, look, Rohan-sensei,
I know a lot has happened
between the two of us…
Why did you heal me?
Huh?
You should've minded
your own business.
I would've rather
wasted away to nothing
than have been saved
by the likes of you.
I told you to run,
but you still stepped right into
the enemy's trap.
You're an ignoramus.
Wha—
By the way, you and I are even now.
Just when it seemed Rohan
was about to turn the page…
On a different note…
Koichi Hirose decided to
go on a walk with his dog.
HIGHWAY GO GO
Ah, a British Shorthair.
Where'd you come from,
little sweetie?
EPISODE 30
CATS LOVE YOSHIKAGE KIRA